Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
I'd have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know.
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As Imake foes of the world
I'm bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Now, this is the comeback the time to awaken is now
The sky, dark and foreboding...
...as the storm intensifies!
Across Onigashima...
...the Blue Dragon's bellow!
The mad howling of a legion of beasts!
At the Port of Habu...
...the passing of a seasonal shower...
...dyes the leaves
of the maple in autumn's red!
This is a tale of loyalty,
of the retainers who risked it all
to avenge their lord, Kozuki Oden!
Though I may lack in eloquence...
Yes!
Red Scabbards!
...I shall do my best
to recount the details.
Now...!
Upon twilight of the day
of the Fire Festival,
before a stormy, rain-filled night...
Leaving behind the
boisterous Flower Capital,
Momonosuke and his retinue make their way toward
Tokage Port, attempting to catch up to Luffy.
Eh?!
Are you not going out to sea, Yamato?!
Aye, I am not!
I have already told Luffy and his crew!
So you are staying, Yamato.
Should I not?
Nay, 'tis reassuring
to have you here...
But did you not say something about
making a decision earlier?
Ah, yes....
Oden began by traveling
across this country, did he not?
I know so little
of the world myself!
So I shall follow in his footsteps,
one day setting out to sea!
That is my decision!
What's this?!
Luffy and his crew already
discussed this with you, Yamato?!
This angers me all the more!
They dare mock me unto the end!
Why do they depart without bidding
either me or Kin'emon farewell?!
Why?
Your name?
Your father was a fool of a lord.
Who might you be,
and what business brings you here?
I'm Luffy.
The future Pirate King!
You, a samurai?!
Whatta load!
Well, I'm gonna be the Pirate King
one day, so there, knucklehead!
Then / shall be Shogun of the
Land of Wano one day, you buffoon!
Whuzzat, ya slimy eel?!
Arrogant monkey!
Who ya callin' a monkey?!
Are you just a puppet, Momo?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
I wish to fell Kaido!
Let's team up.
An alliance!
Luffy!
That's right, Momo!
You're...
...just some topknotted runt,
always bossin' people around
even though you're just a dumb scaredy-cat!
Do what ya gotta to stay alive!
I'm gonna rescue you,
no matter what!
'Cause we're pals!
I'll ask one more time, runt.
What's your name?!
Hear my name!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
I am...
...the future Shogun...
...of the Land of Wano!
Go, Momo!
You can fly!
Aye!
Go stop...
...Onigashima!
As for Kaido,
I'm gonna...
...one hundred percent...
beat him!
We may not be the best of friends,
but we journeyed together for so long,
and yet you feel nothing?!
How horrible you are!
I thought you a better man than that, Luffy!
He confuses freedom with disrespect!
Am I not right, Kin'emon?!
You are most correct!
If I might inquire, Momonosuke-sama,
why do you not take flight?
Silence!
Yes, sir!
apologize for my rudeness!
You are the true Shogun of Wano now,
Momonosuke-sama!
Depending on Luffy-dono's response,
it is regretful, but we may have to cut him down!
Indeed! Such is
the way of the samurai!
You said we were pals, Luffy!
You needn't be so angry...
He humiliated me!
He shall pay!
First, I punch!
Then, bite!
And then... Ah...
Whatever the case,
I will bring him to bear!
Next time I see you guys,
we're total enemies.
No complaints,
not even if I murder you all.
Nope, won't hear any from me!
Bye, Traf!
Shuddup.
Whuuuuh?!
Later, Jaggy!
You're next in line
to be ground meat.
Shove off and ship out!
Hey!
You lot, there!
Wait one moment!
Hey! We came to send you off!
Momonosuke, Kin'emon!
Yamato-chwan!
Luffy!
Uweeeh?!
I have you now!
Luffy!
What are you thinking!!
Leaving without a word to us,
we who have known you for longer than any other?!
Heeh?!
You have incensed the Shogun and myself!
Explain yourself at once!
Well, we're meetin' now, ain't we?
Luffy...
By order of the Shogun...
W-Whaddya want?
Dod't go!
V'll mizz you!
Pweaze, stay with me! Forevuh!
I do not want to be
separated from you all!
You were the very reasons...
...for my continued existence!
...I was able to smile!
I thank you for avenging...
...my father and mother!
I am weak of mind,
and cannot find the words...
But, I fear what is to come!
So please, do not go!
Kinda pathetic, huh...
Momo-chan's still just a child...
Usopp!
Gotcha, it's all set!
Catch!
We were standin' by on the Sunny
so we could hand this over to ya!
Some Shogun" you are, Momo!
You might be bigger in size,
but we know who ya are on the inside!
Yer just a stupid dumbhead scaredy-cat!
But...
...I think of ya
as my little brother.
This is...
A flag?
When the times get tough,
just remember our adventure on the seas!
An' fly this over Wano!
If trouble comes knockin',
just flash this at 'em!
If someone picks a fight with one of us,
they're pickin' a fight with all of us!
"One of us"?
You mean, I am one of you?
Kin'emon, Yamato....
Momo!
If yous wanna be pirates,
we'll come by to pick ya up anytime!
And no wimps allowed!
Set sail!
Steady as she goes!
I'm counting on you, Yamato!
Mmm!
Later!
All the best!
Aye!
Hang in there, Shogun!
Good luck, Momonosuke!
No sobbin' from now on!
Look after yourselves!
We'll meet again!
Take care!
Kin'emon?
Yes, m'lord?
I shall surpass Kozuki Oden someday!
And I shall see it through!
Surpass me?
No, not you!
Okay...
To Hakumai!
was told there's an official port
with a lift to lower ships.
Thank goodness!
Having climbed a waterfall to get here,
I thought we would also be plunging off!
Ah! Straw Hat and Trafalgar...
Usin' the official port, huh?
Somethin' regular-ass pirates
like you oughta use!
Cause after all,
it's nice 'n harmless!
Harm...
...less?
Perfect for followers like you!
Follow...
...ers?!
No, don't, Luffy!
Harmless is good!
Don't take the bait!
Huh?
Captain, why're you makin' that face?
Using the official port's totally okay!
Shaddup and just follow me!
Got it!
You don't got it!
Stop the Captain!
Jinbe, lemme take the helm!
Don't do it, Luffyyyy!
Captain, just don't!
The fellow rebels that Momonosuke-sama
and Kin'emon brought in tow...
As though they were
the true Wisdom Kings,
they raged on like typhoons!
Neither the Dragon King, Kaido,
nor the monstrous Oiran-fiend,
could match their fury!
Their death throes
rent the sky asunder!
Meanwhile, there was Orochi,
thought to have burned to death!
Out of spite, he threw himself
upon the Princess Hiyori!
Slash!
And just like that, with a single swipe of the blade,
someone cut him down...
Twas none other than
Kozuki Oden's second disciple, Denjiro!
And so, Orochi's remaining head
was set ablaze!
Such was the end
of Kurozumi Orochi!
Much like the rumbling of thunder,
so fell Onigashima
and the Dragon King, Kaido!
The dark clouds...
...cast across the skies of
the Land of Wano for some twenty-odd years...
...ever so...
...Slowly clear away.
With the sounds of the Flower Capital's
festival music in the distance...
Roll!
Burning like mad,
Orochi, ever-glaring
in our direction, said this:
"The Kurozumi Clan's grudge...
"...will curse this country
for generations to come!"
One could see the twenty years
of Wano's suffering in Princess Hiyori's eyes!
Then, her gaze of steadfastness!
Tis dangerous, Hiyori-sama!"
Cried Denjiro the samurai,
but she brushed him aside.
Our beloved Princess Hiyori gave not
any quarter to the burning Orochi!
Instead, she spoke to him his requiem!
Fan in hand...
...bearing the Kozuki family crest.
She bit upon her lip,
recalling the twenty years of anguish.
"O Father, O Mother, O Brother..."
And she thought
of her homeland, and said!
Yeah!
I've been waiting for this!
Come, dear audience!
"If it does not burn...
Kurozumi
"...then it is not charcoal!"
Upon twilight of the day
of the Fire Festival...
The "Reversed Crescent Moon,"
marking the port of rendezvous
Tis a tale of the bloody battles...
...to take revenge, to rebuild a clan...
...that shall be passed down
for generations to come!
Such is the tale of...
the return of these
legendary samurai!
My time here today
is just about at its end!
If you might permit me
pause for today....
hope that we...
...might meet again!
Where shall we fly the flag?
"Time's up"
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly